# Damjan Pjević,

a student at the School of Economics and Business

Contact damjan@pjevic.com

Online presence www.pjevic.com linkedin.com/in/pjevic

# PERSONAL STATEMENT

An ambitious, reliable and open-minded individual with a great passion in tech and business. With a Bachelors in Multimedia Engineering focused on Digital Communication, I am in pursuit of my master's degree in Business Informatics at the School of Economics and Business in Ljubljana.

Experienced with working with the clients, public speaking and working in a team and with a working history in the fields of the computer software industry, event organisation, digital media and marketing.

#### **SKILLS**

Marketing & PR Content creation, verbal communication,

promotional events.

Programming Java, JavaScript, Python, HTML & CSS,

WordPress.

IT Website management, mobile application

development, basics in telecommunications.

Languages Slovenian C2, English C2, Serbian B2,

German B1, Russian A1.

#### **EXPERIENCES**

# Epicoro [2021–now]

#### Web developer

- Building basic and intermediate websites using Elementor and Wordpress for various small and medium sized companies.
- Helping out with live streaming, photography and video editing.
- Restructuring processes using work management software (ClickUp, Notion).

Chamber of Commerce and Industry of Slovenia [2019–2021]

#### **Technical Assistant**

- Independently overseeing technical aspect and providing support for online events with around 10 speakers and more than 100 participants carried out in English or Slovenian.
- Recorded and edited over 50 videos (presentations and reportages) for various events.

Value Add Games [2019–2020]

# Website manager & Content creator

- Helped in marketing with the launch of their most successful product.
- · Re-established the online shop.
- Maintained the website and the online shop.

#### **EDUCATION**

[2020–2022] Business Informatics – Masters.
School of Economics and Business.

University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

[2015–2019] Multimedia Engineering – Bachelors.

Average grade: 9.0

Faculty of Electrical Engineering, University of Ljubljana, Slovenia

Hochschule für Kunst Bremen, Germany

(Erasmus Exchange 2017)

[2021] Google Project Management Certificate,

Coursera

# Selected class projects

- Extension of the Pan-European Mobile Emergency Application with extended reality.
- Using Android SDK created and designed a translation app for one of the Slovene dialects.

### **Extracurriculars**

[2019] Took part in the BEST Summer Course in

Wroclaw, Poland that focuses on company management and how technology and good marketing strategy can embrace its

success.

[2016 – 2019] Took part in various promotional events of

the faculty.

[2012 – 2015] Took part in three different YouthPass

exchanges all focused on international

Peer-to-Peer communication.

[2011 – 2015] High School Debate club.

#### **AWARDS**

[2017] Reached top 20 out of 350 global

teams in OnePlus Student Marketing

Challenge.

[2016] Regional winners in global competition

OSCE

Peer to Peer: Challenging Extremism by a successfully developed and pitched tool for challenging violent extremism.